Lesson 20 Pioneer Pilots. In 1908 Lord Northcliffe offered a prize of $1,000 to the first man who would fly across the
第20课先锋飞行员。1908年，诺斯克利夫勋爵（Lord Northcliffe
English Channel. Over a year passed before the first attempt was made. On July 19,
英语频道。在第一次尝试之前，一年多了。7月19日
1,909. In the early morning, Hubert Latham took off from the French coast in his plane that Antoinette Ivey.
1,909。在清晨，休伯特·拉瑟姆（Hubert Latham）乘飞机从法国海岸起飞，安托瓦内特·艾维（Antoinette Ivey）。
He had traveled only seven miles across the channel when his engine failed and he was forced to land
当他的引擎故障时，他只穿过频道七英里，被迫着陆
on sea. The Antoinette floated on the water until Latham was picked up by a ship.
在海上。安托瓦内特（Antoinette）漂浮在水上，直到莱瑟姆被船捡起。
Calais: n.   加来（法国港市）
Two days alter. Lewis Blarriad arrived near Calais with a plane called NO. 11. Blarriad had been
两天改变。刘易斯·布拉里亚德（Lewis Blarriad）带着一架名为no的飞机到达了加来附近。11。布拉里亚德一直是
making planes since 1905 and this was his Latte's model. A week before, he had completed a successful
自1905年以来制造飞机，这是他的拿铁车的模型。一周前，他完成了成功
overland: adj. 陆上的
overland flight during which he covered 26 miles. Latham, however, did not give up easily. He,
在陆上飞行，他覆盖了26英里。但是，莱瑟姆并不容易放弃。他，
Calais: n.   加来（法国港市）
too, arrived near Calais on the same day with a new Antoinette. It looked as if there would be an
同时，同一天，带着新的安托瓦内特（Antoinette）到达了加来。看起来好像会有
exciting race across the channel. Both planes were going to take off on July 25th, but Latham failed
激动人心的比赛遍布整个频道。两架飞机都将在7月25日起飞，但拉瑟姆失败了
to get up early enough. After making a short test flight at 4.15am, Blarriad set off half an hour later.
足够早。在凌晨4.15进行了短暂的测试飞行后，Blarriad在半小时后出发。
His great flight lasted 37 minutes. When he landed near Dover, the first person to greet him was a
他的出色飞行持续了37分钟。当他降落在多佛附近时，第一个向他打招呼的人是
local policeman. Latham made another attempt a week later and got within half a mile of Dover.
当地警察。一周后，莱瑟姆（Latham）再次尝试了多佛（Dover）半英里处。
But he was unlucky again. His engine failed and he landed on the sea for the second time.
但是他又不幸了。他的引擎失败，他第二次降落在海上。